* Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**Collecting information:**  
When enrolling on Android Zone, users are asked for personal identification information such as: username and email address. If you log into Android Zone with a social networking credential, such as with your Twitter or Google+ account, we will ask permission to access basic information from that account, such as your name and email address. You can stop sharing that information with us at any time by removing Android Zone access to that account.

Each user is also identified by the IP address.  
IP addresses of messages sent by users are stored to prevent and combat violations of the Regulation.

E-mail addresses are used to register, validate your account, change your password, or receive notifications according to your settings.  
Messages (posts) are stored in the forum database.

Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers.

However, if you believe that copyright has been infringed by posting messages on our forum, we may not disclose the personally identifiable information of the author, and the disclosure of such data to third parties is not permitted unless expressly agreed of the data subject.

**Cookies:** Third-Party Cookies are placed by third-party advertising platforms or networks in order to deliver ads and track ad performance, or enable advertising networks to deliver ads that may be relevant to you based upon your activities (this is sometimes called "behavioral tracking" or "targeted" advertising) on the Site. They may subsequently use information about your visit to target you with advertising that you may be interested in on the Site and other websites. 

**Privacy Practices for Advertising:**  
We respect your right to privacy throughout all of the services we provide. You can opt out of third party interest-based advertising from NAI members by using the **[NAI's opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!%2F)**.

### Third Parties

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

**reCAPTCHA V2**

This site uses a CAPTCHA to ensure humans are performing certain actions. The CAPTCHA provider may set a session cookie and get information about your internet browser and device accessing this website.

**Data processing:**  
The personal data you provide us is administered safely and only for the specific purpose of this community, creating an active account for using and viewing the forum.  
  
Registered users give their consent to the processing of personal data, under the conditions mentioned above, in accordance with applicable laws.

ANDROID ZONE, New York, New York, New York, 10005

* Privacy Policy

    *  English (USA) (Default)
        
    *  Deutsch
        
    *  Español (España)
        
    *  Elegant - Light (Default)
        
    *  Villain - Dark Theme

* #### [Browse](#)
    
* #### [Activity](#)
    
    * #### [My Activity Streams](#)

* Create New...

Important Information
---------------------

This website uses cookies. To learn more, visit our [Privacy Policy](https://android-zone.ws/privacy/).

 Change theme
